http://www.pni.org.uk/about-pni/pni-org-uk-privacy-policy/

Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from most pages of our site and on our registration page.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all personal information collected or submitted on the PNI ORG UK website. In order to use some of the features on the PNI ORG UK site you are asked to register as a member. The personal information collected at registration is:
A username of your choice
Email address
Date of Birth
Gender
Use and Storage of your Personal Information
When you supply any personal information to PNI ORG UK (e.g. for registrations, chat comments, topics, posts or private messages etc), we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must collect the information fairly; that is, we must explain how we will use it and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.
Any personal information you provide to PNI ORG UK will only be used within PNI ORG UK. It will NEVER be supplied to anyone outside PNI ORG UK without first obtaining your consent, unless we are required by law to disclose it.
We will never sell our members e-mail addresses.
About Cookies and the Way We Use Them
In common with other websites, we do use “cookies”. A cookie is a small file that a Website puts on your hard drive so that it can remember something about you at a later time. Our system uses a cookie to record a unique reference on your computer so that we can keep track of your local sites. You can control the use of cookies on your computer and can turn them on or off at anytime (please refer to your internet browser). However, if you do turn cookies off you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. You can get more information about cookies at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. In order that we can monitor and improve the site, we may gather certain information about you when you use it, including details of your domain name and IP address, operating system, browser version. Please note: We do not use cookies to store any of your personal information held on your computer.
3rd Party Advertising Cookies
Some adverts on our pages come from third party sources; some of these third parties use their own anonymous cookies to track how many people have seen a particular ad, or to track how many people have seen it more than once. The companies that generate these cookies have their own, very strict, privacy policies, and we have no access to read or write these cookies.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, no part of our website is structured to attract minors.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these policies; please send us an email at enquiries@pni.org.uk
About Us
Contact us
Member Initiatives
Our Forum
Our Founder
Patrons of PNI ORG UK
PNI ORG UK Charity Details
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Testimonials
Tweets by @PNIORGUK
Donate now to support our Charity
Donate via Everyclick
About us
PNI ORG UK was established in 1998 by Veritee Reed Hall. It is a
registered charity, No. 1113840.
Read more »
Help from real women
We are not medical professionals or 'experts' in PNI, this site was founded by women who have suffered or are suffering Post Natal Illness. Therefore we urge you not to rely on any information you have gained from this web site or any other web site or information service, as a diagnosis.
Contact us
If you want to get in touch with PNI ORG UK, please use the following methods...
Get in touch »
Copyright © 2020 pni.org.uk. All rights reserved.
Charity number 1113840.
Socialise with us on Twitter or Facebook
Home
What is PNI?
